Penny, is it weird that
we're having girls' night here,
(Amy:)but you don't
live here anymore,
(Amy:)so it's basically
my girls' night?
(Penny:)I hadn't really
thought about it.
(Amy:)But now you're thinking about it
and it bothers you?
(Amy:)I get that.
(Bernadette:)Things going well with you
and Sheldon living together?
(Amy:)Better than ever.
(Amy:)He asks about my day,
takes an interest in my life.
(Amy:)He's like my boyfriend
in college,
(Amy:)except he's real,
so people can see him.
(Bernadette:)I've been seeing him for years,
(Bernadette:)I'm still not convinced
he's real.
(Penny:)Hey, can I
ask you a question?
(Penny:)You've been married
for a while.
(Penny:)Is it normal
for the husband
(Penny:)to kind of completely stop
giving a crap?
Uh-oh, what's going on?
(Penny:)Well, Leonard used to
do all these things,
(Penny:)like bring me flowers
(Penny:)and wear pants.
(Bernadette:)It's okay,
Howie never has on pants.
(Bernadette:)The Domino's guy brings
the pizza like this now.